# GERALD ROMERO

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Graduated as a Cum Laude at the University of Batangas, majoring in Bachelor of Science in Computer Science. I have slight but solid work experience as a freelance web developer and an IT support specialist intern. I have developed a substantial amount of personal projects.

# SKILLS

- Web Development with React JS, Firebase, NoSQL, MySQL, Node JS, and Tailwind CSS.
- Mobile Development with JavaScript, React Native, Firebase, NoSQL, and Tailwind CSS.
- Ability to use Git and GitHub.

#### **EDUCATION**

## **COMPUTER SCIENCE**

University of Batangas, Batangas City Cum Laude | July 2020 - Aug 2024

## **BEST IN THESIS**

ChatNB: An AI Driven Chatbot Utilizing Natural Language Processing to facilitate conversation with Notable Batangueños.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## WEB DEVELOPER (FREELANCE)

Protected Area Management Board of Mts. Palay Palay/Mataas Na Gulod Dec 2023 - Jan 2024

Developed a booking website, enhancing user experience and functionality.

Implemented responsive design techniques to ensure compatibility across various devices and browsers.

## IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST INTERN

TaskUs July 2023- Sep 2023

Developed an IT scheduling system to manage employee attendance, absences, and leave requests.

Conducted thorough testing and troubleshooting to identify and resolve issues, ensuring system reliability and efficiency.

### CONTACT

devgeraldromero@gmail.com devgeraldr.github.io +639568577636 linkedin.com/in/gerald-romero-732424279 Batangas City, Batangas,